against China.
維持貨幣包。
第一手住宅物業。
Credential measures by the Hong Kong Monetary Authority.
on the development of financial services industry in Hong Kong.
委員支持誒，委員咧，各位委員咧係支持務委員會嘅工作咧。啊，本人僅此陳詞。
梁繼昌議員就財經事務委員會二零一七至二零一八年度報告向本會發言，梁繼昌議員。
成員支持行政總署提出的倡議，促進和推動綠色金融發展。
On Hong Kong's macroeconomic issues, members have expressed concern about the impacts of a possible trade war between China and the United States.
主席，在我的職能是主席團成員，我提交報告和工作，對今年主席團的工作進行總結，並概述一些主要的工作領域。
成員們有提出關於資金外流從香港，產生於美國利率提高和預期本地利率上升的問題。
成員們也敦促HKMA devise a regulatory regime of cryptocurrencies in light of increasing prevalence of the investment product, amount investors and the high risks involved.
Besides urging the administration to formulate contingency measures to prepare Hong Kong for the possible shocks, members have called on senior government officials to visit the U.S. to lobby the U.S. government for exempting Hong Kong from the trade restrictive measures imposed.
就係
一些成員已敦促行政會考慮放寬抵押貸款的按揭比率，以協助潛在買家繳付首期，並引入空置税，對未售出的樓盤徵收。
Regarding the work of HKMA, the panel notes that the weak side convertibility undertaking of the linked exchange rate system has been triggered several times since April 2018, which subsequently cost HKMA to buy Hong Kong dollar to.
質詢第一項質詢擴進語言。
在Areas包括電子支付系統，和使用的Blockchain技術。
我歡迎行政工作在促進金融技術（FinTech）簡稱）。
The new listing regime for emerging and innovative companies was implemented on 30 April 2008.
我亦都樂意借呢個機會，感謝所有成員、委員會及秘書處支持委員會的工作。多謝。
which mainly seeks to allow the listing of pre-venue by biotech issuers and companies with weighted voting rights structures.
成員們已表達了多種觀點，對納入金融服務發展委員會作為有限公司有限保證的公司。
和 enhancing protection to investors of companies with weighted voting rights, given that a class action regime is not available in Hong Kong.
成員們已強調，對於行政和金融監管機構加強推動金融科技發展和應用的重要性。
While members in general welcome the new listing regime, they have stressed the need to strike a balance between the increasing competitiveness of Hong Kong's listing regime.
Some members have also urged the Hong Kong Exchanges and Clearing Company Limited to consider expanding the scope of pre-revenue companies under the new regime, so that more local companies can benefit from the regime.